# Joaquín Mesa

Buenos Aires, Argentina · joacomesa@gmail.com · Linkedin: Joaquín Mesa · Portfolio: joacomesa.com.ar

# FRONT-END DEVELOPER & DESIGNER

Front-end developer with a focus on UX and advanced Digital Communication student. My skills as a developer are complemented by my knowledge in design and user experience. Also, artificial intelligence has become a fundamental tool in my professional life. I am a consistent, resourceful, and self-taught person who enjoys teamwork and am always open to learn new skills and technologies.

#### **SKILLS**

Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React JS, Tailwind, Bootstrap, Sass,

Astro, Next JS, SQL, PHP

Tools: GitHub, Git, Firebase, Figma,

Photoshop, Wordpress

Others: UX / UI Design, Wireframing,

Prototyping, SEO

Languages: Spanish, English (C1 IELTS)

# **EXPERIENCE**

# Freelance Web Developer & Designer

January 2023 - Present

- Web interface designing in Figma
- Development, deployment and maintenance of accesible, scalable and responsive websites
- Communication with clients

# Project Management Internship - Delateral

December 2023 - August 2024

Trainee role

- Collaboration in branding, communication and digital marketing projects
- Websites and web platforms management
- Weekly meetings with the team and clients

# **Assistant Professor** - University of Palermo

August 2023 - July 2024

In two subjects:

Digital Production III (Web Development | HTML - CSS - JS - PHP - SQL) - Prof. Mariano Ingerto Interactive Communication III (UX / UI Design) - Prof. Álvaro Ghisolfo

- Professor assistance,
- Lesson planning
- Student support with coding and design projects

Data Entry - Fundación Kaleidos

December 2021 - January 2022

- Data entry in Wordpress
- Microsoft Excel
- Multimedia searching, selecting and editing

# **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor's Degree in Digital Communication**

University of Palermo 2021 - Present

# **COMPLEMENTARY EDUCATION**



**Front-end React Development** Coderhouse



**UX / UI Specialization** 

California Institute of Arts - Coursera